<data>
  <c1152143449>
    <name>Kevin</name>
    <text>What a great website!!!</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2006 Jul 05 07:50:49 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1152143449>
  <c1152143467>
    <name>Paintball Joe</name>
    <text>Great place</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2006 Jul 05 07:51:07 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1152143467>
  <c1152306013>
    <name>matt</name>
    <text>nice park, really cheap pricesincluding paint!!!...very helpfull staff.</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2006 Jul 07 05:00:13 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1152306013>
  <c1162752307>
    <name>Daves Creek Youth Group</name>
    <text>Our youth group loved playing on your field!  Thank you so much for all the help and attention you gave our boys.  I can not tell you how many times we've been asked when we are coming back!!  Thank you so much for everything!!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2006 Nov 05 01:45:07 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1162752307>
  <c1164567868>
    <name>Duane Mize</name>
    <text>My son and I have played at several locations in the Tampa Florida area, but none are as accomodating, or family friendly as Mr. Lester's place.  Not only were the fields in great shape, clean, and easily accessible, but the price was right and pro-shop was like none other complete with custom guns Mr. Lester had built himself and all the accessories. It has instantly become our family's Thanksgiving day tradition!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2006 Nov 26 02:04:28 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1164567868>
  <c1176584645>
    <name>Jason Burns</name>
    <text>We had a small group from our church come down and had a great time!  Super course, awesome service, and great pro shop.  Not just a good place to play but a good place to shop!  Even got help with custom screws when one of our guns broke . . . excellent!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2007 Apr 14 05:04:05 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1176584645>
  <c1177255546>
    <name>Jarod Brumley </name>
    <text>We just came from Alabama to visit relatives, but my uncle told us about this awsome paintball and airsoft place. When we went there the we had the time of our lifes. Then he showed us his shop. All I say is that It was the best place I've been in all of my life.  </text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2007 Apr 22 11:25:46 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1177255546>
  <c1187287792>
    <name>Amir Windom</name>
    <text>Me and my brother drove from Stone Mountain, Georgia which is about and hour and a half away.  We were the only 2 at Wendell's course and what a nice course it was.  The castle he built was astonishing.  It looked like it belonged on the set of a broadway play.  There are great shot angles as places to duck for cover.  My brother and I really really enjoyed ourselves and the trip down to Greenville was well worth it.  What made even more worth it was the kind gentleman Wendell Lester who owns, manages and builds the course.  Very kind gentleman who makes you want to support his business just because he's a kind gentleman and makes you feel welcome and appreciated.  His paintball shop is the best shop I've ever seen.  Has everything you could possibly want in the paintball world.  I recommend his course and shop to anyone who's a paintball fanatic.</text>
    <timestamp>Thu 2007 Aug 16 02:09:52 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1187287792>
  <c1190088029>
    <name>Dalton Dudley</name>
    <text>Went up there just to check it out and seemed pretty cool.Really nice guy who owns the place and nice shop too.Has alot of selection.Me and some friends are goin this weekend 2 play.</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2007 Sep 18 12:00:29 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1190088029>
  <c1202601581>
    <name>Kohlhaas Party</name>
    <text>What a wonderful time! We had my son's 11th birthday party here and all 18 people are still talking about the great experience they had. If you are looking for a great, safe, clean, amazing paintball time look no furthur. We called ahead amd Mr. Wendel had everything ready to go. If you love paintballing or are just looking to try it out, this is the place to go.</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2008 Feb 09 06:59:41 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1202601581>
  <c1215922125>
    <name>Braedin Canada</name>
    <text>i came to this piant ball park with four freids. iT was vary clean and the field was well layout and the castle is the best thing. it is the best field ever.

CANADA</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2008 Jul 13 12:08:45 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1215922125>
  <c1226601840>
    <name>Austin Key</name>
    <text>This place is awesome. I was here the other day and I had so much fun. There is only 1 thing! bring alot of ppl</text>
    <timestamp>Thu 2008 Nov 13 01:44:00 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1226601840>
  <c1226715016>
    <name>kelly d.</name>
    <text> My son had his 12th b-day party there and had a great time. The castle and town fields are amazing! I would recomend this paintball field to anyone looking for a day of fun.  Mr. Wendell was so kind and helpful.  Well worth the drive!  He also has a great selection of guns and supplies to purchase - all the guys wished their parents were there to buy lots of new stuff!</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2008 Nov 14 09:10:16 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1226715016>
  <c1229291141>
    <name>AU SigEp</name>
    <text>Great fields!!! Great people.  Mr. Lester and his wife were excellent hosts for our group.  He is has everything you could ask for and the prices are very reasonable as well. We took a group of 40+ people out there and had all three fields to ourselves.  We played all day and couldn't have had a better time.  We will be returning in the very near future.  I would suggest bringing a lot of people. Can't wait to go back!!!!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2008 Dec 14 04:45:41 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1229291141>
  <c1232500863>
    <name>wes austin</name>
    <text>best paintball feilds in the world and the proshop has the best pricing in town or more like the world mr. wendell is great and a very nice man</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2009 Jan 20 08:21:03 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1232500863>
  <c1244931612>
    <name>Michael O </name>
    <text>Played for a bachelor party on the 13th. Enjoyed it very much. Three very strong courses. Lots of detail with the town and castle. VERY friendly and great for people who just want to have a good time.</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2009 Jun 13 06:20:12 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1244931612>
  <c1261617001>
    <name>Duane </name>
    <text>Our family Thanksgiving day tradition continues at Paintball Outfitter! Wendell opened up all the fields, provided outstanding service and allowed us many freedoms and liberties that most Paintball fields wouldn't even consider.  His prices are fair, his fields are improved, his rental equipment is high quality and his personal service is unmatched...Oh by the way don't miss checking out his pro-shop and his one of a kind creations.  We had a great time and would recommend others check out his fields.</text>
    <timestamp>Thu 2009 Dec 24 01:10:01 AM GMT</timestamp>
  </c1261617001>
  <c1266887755>
    <name>MILLER'S 02-20-2010</name>
    <text>Awsome place to play. Family oriented. The boys can't stop talking about it and my daughter wants to get into paintballing after her expeirience there. The castle was a hit with the kids and the town was the best. My youngest son can't wait to get old enough to play. You couldn't have asked for a better service. Their pro shop is unreal anything you can ask for he's got it. His skills are unbelieveable. The long 7 hour drive from Kentucky was well worth it, and we can't wait to go back and have a wonderful time.</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2010 Feb 23 01:15:55 AM GMT</timestamp>
  </c1266887755>
  <c1267057981>
    <name>cody, kentucky boy</name>
    <text>GREAT PLACE TO PLAY!!!!...idk how many paintball fields there are in Georgia, but ill bet he can beat it, he'll do anything you need for a paintball gun, airsoft gun, and laser tag...He's a great guy, his place is safe, fun, and very well maintained,,I cant wait till i can play there again.</text>
    <timestamp>Thu 2010 Feb 25 12:33:01 AM GMT</timestamp>
  </c1267057981>
  <c1289273970>
    <name>Bulloch Proof</name>
    <text>I come to Paintball outfitter Once a week. This is one of the best fields around and it get better each time

I run www.bestscenariogames.com and I use Paintball Outfitter for all the scenario games I host Check it out and you will see why </text>
    <timestamp>Mon 2010 Nov 08 10:39:30 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1289273970>
  <c1290391516>
    <name>Todd Stallman</name>
    <text>Another great Airsoft game at PBO this past Saturday 11/20/10 at PBO.  It was moslty all  PWNY and we had a great time. If your looking to get into Airsoft on an awesome field, come out and get with us at one of our favorite fields which we call PBO. </text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2010 Nov 21 09:05:16 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1290391516>
  <c1291248862>
    <name>Duane Mize</name>
    <text>Year #5 for our family to spend T-day paintballing at Mr. Lester's.  He's added some great attractions, and always provides fantastic service! A great team/family building event!</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2010 Dec 01 07:14:22 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1291248862>
  <c1292115360>
    <name>Todd Stallman</name>
    <text>Fresh off a recent victory at Operation Brushfire in Phenix City with the Area-13 Group, PWNY is back in action at PBO next Sunday 12/19/10 from 1-6pm. If your looking to play some top notch airsoft, come on out and get with PWNY at Paintball-Outfitter. If this is your first time playing no need worry. We'll set you up to run with experienced airsoft players who know the field and game pretty well. Look for Todd aka Digger or any of the PWNY crew and we'll get you hooked up. </text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2010 Dec 11 07:56:00 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1292115360>
  <c1293261835>
    <name>Todd Stallman</name>
    <text>We re-scheduled the game from 12/19/10 to Sunday 1/2/11 from 1-6pm. If you pikced up a new airsoft gun for Christmas, this game would be a good time to break it in. Also any new players to the sport of airsoft are welcome to come out and sling some plastic with PWNY at Paintball-Outfitter. </text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2010 Dec 25 02:23:55 AM EST</timestamp>
  </c1293261835>
  <c1297015228>
    <name>Ross Harrison</name>
    <text>Took 6 boys for a 13th Birthday Party.  The paintball fields, equipment, etc.  were amazing.  Mr. Lester, the owner, was incredibly accommodating.  Truly a great experience and would come back for paintball and airsoft.  Thank you Mr. Lester</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2011 Feb 06 01:00:28 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1297015228>
  <c1300493151>
    <name>Nick Hopek</name>
    <text>Playing a Paintball game tomorrow. We will be meeting at the field at 11 am. There will be 6 - 8 people in our group. If would would like to join us, please feel free to do so.</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2011 Mar 18 08:05:51 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1300493151>
  <c1300655597>
    <name>Nick Hopek</name>
    <text>We had 15 people show up for our paintball game on Saturday. We all had a great time. If you are planning a paintball game, Mr. Wendell has my contact info., please feel free to contact me.</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2011 Mar 20 05:13:17 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1300655597>
  <c1300741511>
    <name>Bulloch Proof</name>
    <text>Had a great time Saturday Had a Birthday party reschedule so me and the wife went to the feild anyway to see what would happen and there were about 19 people and we had free hamburgers and hotdogs had a blast and mades some good contacts for some paintball and airsoft ck: www.bestscenariogames.com </text>
    <timestamp>Mon 2011 Mar 21 05:05:11 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1300741511>
  <c1300741606>
    <name>Bulloch Proof</name>
    <text>www.bestscenariogames.com

is having an overnight scenario in april date to come hamburgers and hotdogs plus outside movie to be played after game.</text>
    <timestamp>Mon 2011 Mar 21 05:06:46 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1300741606>
  <c1301684183>
    <name>DeMarcus Lewis</name>
    <text>Having a paintball tournament Monday april fourth with a 6 to 8 people walk ons welcome</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2011 Apr 01 02:56:23 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1301684183>
  <c1302125095>
    <name>Bulloch Proof</name>
    <text>came to play with Demarcus ther was about 10 or so had fun got to shoot and got shot at ck: www.bestscenariogames.com</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2011 Apr 06 05:24:55 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1302125095>
  <c1302125266>
    <name>Bulloch Proof</name>
    <text>Scenario game (Airsoft)4/31/2011 from 10:00 till 10:00 meal provided $45.00 includes gun 500 rounds mask and meal
$40.00 if you have a gun. see more detals at www.bestscenariogames.com</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2011 Apr 06 05:27:46 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1302125266>
  <c1302125623>
    <name>Lacey Evans</name>
    <text>I went to play airsoft for the first time and I had a blast thanks to Mr. Wendell and Best Scenario Games the Claymore mines were amazing my sister scremed when she triped one best day ever</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2011 Apr 06 05:33:43 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1302125623>
  <c1302125690>
    <name>bestscenariogames com</name>
    <text>Scenario game (Airsoft)4/31/2011 from 10:00 till 10:00 meal provided $45.00 includes gun 500 rounds mask and meal $40.00 if you have a gun. see more detals at www.bestscenariogames.com 
</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2011 Apr 06 05:34:50 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1302125690>
  <c1305224619>
    <name>Best Scenario Games.com</name>
    <text>4-31-11 was a good turn out had steaks and drinks for everyone played till 12am Thanks Mr. Lester</text>
    <timestamp>Thu 2011 May 12 02:23:39 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1305224619>
  <c1305300619>
    <name>Holton workman</name>
    <text>If anyone is playing paintball Friday or Saturday let me know my email-holtonworkman@gmail.com</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2011 May 13 11:30:19 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1305300619>
  <c1306636410>
    <name>Laura Burkhart</name>
    <text>May 28,2011.  We had an airsoft party for our son who just turned 11.  He and all his friends had a blast. My husband and I had fun too.  Mr. Wendell made us feel so welcomed, and he was so accommadating. We used his grill to have a cook out, and anything we forgot to bring with us he got it for us. He made us feel so at home, and has a great sense of humor. I recommend paintball- outfitters to anyone who wants to have a good time outdoors, and have such a great host as Mr. Wendell was.  I know we will be back again! Thanks Mr. Wendell   </text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2011 May 28 10:33:30 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1306636410>
  <c1307373058>
    <name>Sonja Jones</name>
    <text>Dear Wendell,
My guys had a GREAT time playing on your airsoft field. They can't wait to return and fight another day.
Thank you for your hospitality. Fun was had by all!
 
Sonja Jones</text>
    <timestamp>Mon 2011 Jun 06 11:10:58 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1307373058>
  <c1307487611>
    <name>bestscenariogames com</name>
    <text>june 18th anyone welcome airsoft game at 5:00PM till 11:00PM  evening/night game full scenario</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2011 Jun 07 07:00:11 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1307487611>
  <c1309037737>
    <name>Bulloch Proof   with (Echo6)</name>
    <text>July 3rd from 2:00 till 10:00 

Airsoft Game Demolition with real fireworks you plant the bomb in the building and fireworks go off over buildings </text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2011 Jun 25 05:35:37 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1309037737>
  <c1311566324>
    <name>Sigma Phi Epsilon Fraternity Auburn University</name>
    <text>This place is awesome! The fields are great, and Mr. Wendell is the man.</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2011 Jul 24 11:58:44 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1311566324>
  <c1318110055>
    <name>Tracy Purdy</name>
    <text>Awesome fun, great experience at Paitball Outfitter! Highly recommend for all paintball enthusiasts. Very friendly and courteous busines owner. Great for kids and adults.  </text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2011 Oct 08 05:40:55 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1318110055>
  <c1325095484>
    <name>C. Starks - Denver, CO</name>
    <text>Had a great time with the family.  Ages ranged from 16 -66 and everyone had a blast.  I think my 2 sisters had the most fun.  We were taken great care of and will be back the next time we are in town.  This is a must see while you are in the Columbus/LaGrange area.</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2011 Dec 28 01:04:44 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1325095484>
  <c1329605100>
    <name>Steven Newsom</name>
    <text>Trying to start up getting people coming out every sunday for paintball. approx 1pm-whenever. Sermac99@gmail.com if interested or just show up. thanks!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2012 Feb 18 05:45:00 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1329605100>
  <c1329774307>
    <name>Rachel C.</name>
    <text>This place is the best,it has the best Paintball, Laser Tag, and Air Soft I think this place is good for boys and girls, and adults. ( great for birthday party's )</text>
    <timestamp>Mon 2012 Feb 20 04:45:07 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1329774307>
  <c1330147316>
    <name>Jay Jacks      Auburn AL</name>
    <text>Very good time!! Will come back!!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2012 Feb 25 12:21:56 AM EST</timestamp>
  </c1330147316>
  <c1331473059>
    <name>Kim Callahan  Senoia GA</name>
    <text>Had a lot of fun at my daughter's birthday  laser tag party! Thank you!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2012 Mar 11 09:37:39 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1331473059>
  <c1334086342>
    <name>Katy Best Formel   Peachtree City,GA</name>
    <text>My 11 year old had his birthday party here, 6 boys ages 10-16 running around on enormous well appointed field. Mr. Wendell(owner) was personable,polite and professional. We will be back to play soon!!</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2012 Apr 10 03:32:22 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1334086342>
  <c1335673760>
    <name>Shannon Powell  LaGrange, GA</name>
    <text>The birthday party for my 17 yr old son was a great time. Wendell has multiple courses that kept our guys playing for hours. Great time Wendell, thanks so much!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2012 Apr 29 12:29:20 AM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1335673760>
  <c1339189300>
    <name>Auburn Wesley Foundation-Youth Caravan 2012/UMYC and Pine Mt. GA UMYC</name>
    <text>There are lots of different playing fields. many cool obstacles, great equipment,very friendly management! I would definitely suggest this field for big and small groups.---so fun!!</text>
    <timestamp>Fri 2012 Jun 08 05:01:40 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1339189300>
  <c1344383617>
    <name>Tom Quinlan--Yokogana Company</name>
    <text>We really enjoyed our team-building event at Paintball-outfitter. The hospitality and service was outstanding. Thank you for everything.</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2012 Aug 07 07:53:37 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1344383617>
  <c1348099286>
    <name>Wheelabrator Group Sales &amp; Service Team Building Activity</name>
    <text>We had a wonderful time and enjoyed the atmosphere and the equipment was awesome. We enjoyed the experience!!</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2012 Sep 19 08:01:26 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1348099286>
  <c1360520098>
    <name>New Beginning Baptist Church,  Pastor Ken Smith   Senoia, GA</name>
    <text>We had a great time!!</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2013 Feb 10 01:14:58 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1360520098>
  <c1362971907>
    <name>PAINTBALL-OUTFITTER TELEPHONE NUMBER</name>
    <text>     706-882-8721</text>
    <timestamp>Sun 2013 Mar 10 11:18:27 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1362971907>
  <c1380391715>
    <name>Ken Athon   Oakside Baptist Church  LaGrange GA</name>
    <text>Awesome place &amp; facilities! Can't beat the price...excellent!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2013 Sep 28 02:08:35 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1380391715>
  <c1380763826>
    <name>Connie Campbell --- Wheelabrator  LaGrange, GA</name>
    <text>We had a wonderful time playing some friendly competition with our sale and service teams from Canada, Mexico and Us. So very much appreciate the warm hospitality and great opportunity.</text>
    <timestamp>Wed 2013 Oct 02 09:30:26 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1380763826>
  <c1381878237>
    <name>O'CHARLIES Restuarants</name>
    <text>Me and the team had a good outing.Mr. Lester's facility offered several fields to choose from that kept the game challenging. He was very accommodating and we definitely will be back!! Thanks!
</text>
    <timestamp>Tue 2013 Oct 15 07:03:57 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1381878237>
  <c1382230153>
    <name>Phillip &amp; Martha DeBice</name>
    <text>We came for our son's paintball birthday party. They had the best time in the world! Mr. Lester is the nicest gentleman you will ever meet. We will definitely be back!!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2013 Oct 19 08:49:13 PM EDT</timestamp>
  </c1382230153>
  <c1391895765>
    <name>Tuskegee University School of Veterinary Medicine</name>
    <text>We had an awesome time playing paintball!! There are no complaints. Great experience for first time paintballers!</text>
    <timestamp>Sat 2014 Feb 08 04:42:45 PM EST</timestamp>
  </c1391895765>
</data>
